onlinebanglanewspaperlist.com 2018-08-24

# All Bangla Newspaper List - Online Banlga Newspaper list | Bangladesh Govt.approved Bangla Newspaper list | সব বাংলা সংবাদপত্র, বাংলা নিউজপেপার তালিকা একসাথে

### privacy policy

#### privacy policy

We know your official privacy is very much important. So www.allbanglanewspaperlist.com respects your privacy.

**Personal identification information:**

We collect and use your official identification which is used in your website. We provide this identity for helping the user.

**How we use collected information:  **

We firstly collect information and then verify by some of your official. When you sure that this is correct then we use this information to our website. 

**Sharing your personal information:**

Sharing your personal information is 100% secure to us. We use this information only the benifit of your website advertising. We just provide the real data to users. We have the secure archive to save your data. So no tention about your sharing information.

**Third party websites:  **

The third party website is using for linking this sites. Third party website is the main object of our portal. We use thirdpaty website to give user web link to once in a hand. All liability of third party information is the website owner.

**Changes to this privacy policy:**  
Frequently we change our privacy policy. The changing of privacy policy right is reserve by the www.allbanglanewspaperlist.com 

**Advertising:**  
Every one can advertise with our web portal for marketing his or her product. We must see the leagal side of advertising. We do not share any adult contant in our site.

**Trademark sign & Logo's :**  
The logos and registered trademarks used in this website is property of its respective owners.

**Contacting us:**

For any information please write us to:   
Editor@allbanglanewspaperlist.com  
Skype: lionshawon  
Cell: +88 01911789990  
Dhaka, Bangladesh.
